# Ing. Martin Kožený

Phone: (+420) 724 735 822

Email: martin.kozeny@gmail.com

#### Personal

Born on December 21, 1986.

Czech Republic Citizen.

Marital status: single.

Driving licence: yes (B).

Spoken languages: Czech - mothertongue, English - fluent, German - good, French - basic.

#### **Profile**

I have quite a lot experiences with programming in Java (both J2SE and J2EE) and I am also interested in other programming languages and using alternative programming techniques. I passed during my studies many courses related to artifical intelligence which is also object of my interest. In my current work I deal with J2EE technologies and databases.

#### Education

Stanford University Compilers online course, July 2012.

Stanford University Game Theory online course, May 2012.

Ing. Computer science - software engineering, Czech Technical University in Prague, 2009–2012.

International exchange student of computer science, University of New Orleans, 2011.

CISCO Networks certificate, CCNAE 1, 2010.

Bc. Computer science, Czech Technical University in Prague, 2006–2009.

First Certificate in English (FCE), 2006.

Physics Olympiad – regional round: 2nd place 2004, 4th place 2006; national round 2006 – honorable mention.

Grammar school Dašická Pardubice, graduated with honor, 1998–2006.

### **Employment**

Software developer at Arbes Technologies, s.r.o. 2012–present.

Duties: Developing enterprise applications in Spring framework.

Software developer at Ample cz s.r.o. 2007–2012.

Duties: Working on enterprise applications for government and for private sector involving its designing, modeling and implementation. Experiences with databases including data gathering and data normalizing for datawarehouse.

Tourist guide at Kinský dal Borgo, a.s. 2004–2011.

Duties: Tourist guide at castle Kost in summer season.

Ing. Martin Kožený

## Areas of expertise

Programming languages

Java (J2SE, J2EE)

C/C++

Smalltalk

Ruby

Lisp

Prolog

Haskell

**Tools** 

Eclipse

NetBeans

Ant

ETL graphs

Visual Studio

Enterprise Architect, Astah

CVS, SVN, Git

Web Development

JBoss Seam

UML 2.0

Spring

Web Services

Ajax

**Testing** 

CSS

Javascript

HTML XHTML

**JQuery** 

XML

Jakarta Struts

Hibernate

PHP

Databases

SQL language

MS SQL Server

MS SQL Server Analysis

Mondrian

PostgreSQL Server

Oracle and also its PL/SQL extension

MySQL

Administration

Administration of Gnu/Linux

MS Windows

Application server Tomcat

**JBoss** 

Apache

Other

Squander framework

**LATEX** 

DocBook